[{"answer": "It's not here -- I cannot say for sure.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "But is it going to effective to have a peaceful protest now?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Aside from the fact that there has been a loss in trust a long time ago, long before any of the demonstrations even started, there is also a lot of confusion.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "ORGAN: Sarah, why should any Egyptian in Cairo, in Tahrir Square tonight, why should they believe a word that President Mubarak is now saying, given that he's told so many lies particularly in recent weeks and months?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "It looks like it's a real dialogue that's happening right now between the president and the protesters.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "What on earth is going on right now in Cairo right now?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "Well, from what I understand, the director of the CIA quoted media reports and said that they were monitoring it closely and didn't have any additional information.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Did something change or was this always the plan, do you think?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, people have been trying to figure out what's going on for the last 17 days.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Do you believe this plan is going to work?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "The head of state of Egypt is the president who has transmitted all his powers to the vice president.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "Who was the head of state of Egypt right now?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "Well, he's basically saying he's not leaving and the U.S. really wanted him to leave.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "I mean, Wolf, what's happening here is that Mubarak is just simply calling President Obama's bluff, isn't he?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I think to recognize this is very much in the hands of the Egyptian people and they have behaved I would say remarkably.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "Paul Wolfowitz, if you were still at the Defense Apartment, what would you be advising President Obama right now?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "EGROPONTE: Well, it's very, very difficult to tell.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "How do you predict this one to unfurl from where we lie tonight?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, that's hard to tell.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "Mr. Negroponte, from a diplomatic point of view, you being at the sharp end of this behind the corridors negotiations many times, what do you suspect is now happening that we don't know about?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "I don't think we know that.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "General Myers, when you saw that message from Mohammed Elbaradei, has he got a point, do you think, that we may see the situation disintegrate now into what will be a military situation?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Again, I don't think we know.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Does he have a point or is that fanciful, do you think?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "I think they have about a half million men in uniform and another half a million in the reserves.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "How effective are they?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, it is actually great rhetoric, but I don't know that it means very much.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Should we feel encouraged by what you've just heard?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "Well, you know, you can draw all scenarios.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "Finally, General Myers, could you envision any situation where the American military might have to get involved here?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "Remember that the median age in Egypt is 24 years old.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "I mean, what is going to happen next?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "Well, Egypt is the largest Arab country in the world.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "Could we see potentially the unthinkable -- it would have certainly been a month ago -- of the house of Saud becoming imperiled by what is going on?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Surely, yes.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Could this revolution have happened without Twitter, Facebook, the Internet?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, that's a good sign.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "How are they managing to stay so calm and peaceful, when inside they must be burning with anger?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "No, I don't think so.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Do you think he will, Aladdin?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "I think a week.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Rafat, yes or no?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Piers, that fear always exists.", "docId": "110210pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Are you beginning to feel slightly fearful that the peace we've been seeing may go into inevitable bloodshed tomorrow?", "qSentId": 557}]